<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-01-24T00:55:35-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">☁️</title><entry><title type="html">trying to bring howard back to life</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2022/01/23/trying-to-bring-howard-back-to-life.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="trying to bring howard back to life" /><published>2022-01-23T15:30:00-08:00</published><updated>2022-01-23T15:30:00-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2022/01/23/trying-to-bring-howard-back-to-life</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2022/01/23/trying-to-bring-howard-back-to-life.html">&lt;p&gt;Spent most of the winter analyzing and messing around with the different markets/lines and narrowed it down to o/u on props and the total.
Have a clear idea on what extra components I need to add to finish my betting system. Decided I’m going to name the model after howard from uncut gems lol. My puts are doing well, so it’ll probably yield enough money to systematically bet at least until the playoffs. Going to watch them this week and then cash out when the system is closer to being finalized. Set up my machine at home to do training remotely (need to verify the gpu drivers one more time though.) Jonah got a mining rig and said he’d be down to help with training assuming I can actually pull this off.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Spent most of the winter analyzing and messing around with the different markets/lines and narrowed it down to o/u on props and the total. Have a clear idea on what extra components I need to add to finish my betting system. Decided I’m going to name the model after howard from uncut gems lol. My puts are doing well, so it’ll probably yield enough money to systematically bet at least until the playoffs. Going to watch them this week and then cash out when the system is closer to being finalized. Set up my machine at home to do training remotely (need to verify the gpu drivers one more time though.) Jonah got a mining rig and said he’d be down to help with training assuming I can actually pull this off.</summary></entry></feed>